ILGWU. Central Pennsylvania District photographs 5780/090 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Includes: meetings; Washington, D.C.
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Includes: Christmas, retirees
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Includes: Crystal strike, 1987; chorus, 1986; Local 93 on strike at Allura; rally in Washington, D.C.; meetings; office; party; "Veto the Veto" "Stop importing unemployment," rally in Washington, D.C.
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Includes: American Red Cross awards; meetings; workers in shops; workers in costume; New York World's Fair, 1964-1965; health care
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Includes: protest of Jomax; nursery, 1953; meetings; class; workers in shop; health care; retirees; on strike at Judy Bond
- Mixed photographs Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Includes: civil right rally; rally in Washington, D.C.; Union Label Department; meatcutters' strike; political committee; York retirees, Lancaster shop, Unity [House?], Scotty, Bernstein, strike committee [?], Maryville; President Lyndon B. Johnson; press retiree, Dr. Anne, consumers conference, York class; Esther P., retirees, York class, Marysville, community service
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Includes: rally in Washington, D.C.; proest of Scranton Ripper Bill (unemployment compensation); meetings, David Dubinsky; Union Label, Miss ILGWU; meeting with Esther Peterson; Philadelphia; 1965 ILGWU Convention
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Includes: meetings; on strike at Judy Bond; Husen Blouse; community service, Union Label convention
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Includes: meetings; on strike at Judy Bond; rally for Lyndon B. Johnson; community service; Union Label; Unity House
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Includes: meetings; Cameron Dress, Marty farewell; politics; Scranton protest; ILGWU laboratory plaque
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Includes: meetings, Scranton protest, Washington, D.C. [?]
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 20)
  Includes: meetings, workers in shop
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 21)
  Includes: meetings; Sol Chaikin; Kaspar Manufacturing Company
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 22)
  Includes: meetings, Washington, D.C.
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 23)
  Includes: meetings, retirees, rally
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 24)
  Includes: meetings, group photos, New York World's Fair, rally in Scranton (unemployment compensation), performance
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 25)
  Includes: Union Label dresses, meetings, performance, rally, workers in shop
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 26)
  Includes: meetings, protests, York County Labor Council
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 27)
  Includes: parade float, recreation, performance, Mobile Health Center, Local 93 protest
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 28)
  Includes: meetings, rallies, flood [?]
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 29)
  Includes: United Fund award to Cameron Dress, 1962; meetings, dinners, Christmas
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 30)
  Includes: retirees, meetings, Childrens Development Center, recreation
- Mixed photographs and negatives (Box 6, Folder 31)
  Includes: meetings; workers in shops; Herbie's retirement party; first aid class
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 32)
  Includes: parties; meetings; health care; "voteck" high school
- Mixed photographs and negatives 1963 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  Includes: meetings; graduation; ILGWU convention, 1975; William Penn Memorial Museum; strikers at Judy Bond; rally in baseball stadium; members of Central Pennsylvania District going to Washington, D.C.
- Mixed photographs and negatives 1963 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  Includes: members of Dressmakers Joint Council outside of Eileen Hope; Pennsylvania staff in Allentown, 1963; performance; Weis meet department strikers outside of Weis Markets; members at rally "For 'Jobs and Freedom'"; group photos, including David Dubinsky; convention, 1971; inaugural parade; York Fair, strike, Union Label York, Weis picket, Union Label Harrisburg, Milton Shapp
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 35)
  Includes: workers in shops, meeting, Union Label dresses, awards
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 36)
  Includes: visit to Robert Walker office; Local 197, strike at Lititz Sportswear; Pennsylvania Farmers Association; first aid class; Local 108, strike at Lewistown Sportswear; food drive; building of Northeast Department, Western Pennsyvania district, Locals 424, 455; portraits
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 37)
  Includes: meetings, Sargent Shriver, retirees, Louis Stulberg, convention, shop ballots
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 38)
  Includes: retirees, workers in shops, American Red Cross event, Louis Stulberg, anniversary party, members and parade float, meetings, dinner, Union Label dresses, Christmas, Joe Glazer signing "Songs of Work and Freedom"
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 39)
  Includes: meetings, welcoming Muriel Humphrey, workers in shops,York County Labor Council, AFL-CIO parade float; Central Pennsylvania District welcomed to Hawaii; Unioin Label dresses
- Photographs and negatives 1967 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  Includes: classes, meetings, parties, workers in shops
- Mixed photographs (Box 6, Folder 41)
  Includes: meetings, workers in shops, parties
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Includes: meetings; party; Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers International Union of America apprentice contest; graphics; miscellaneous text; laundry workers protest
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Includes: Lancaster class; meetings; Pennsylvania AFL-CIO; Hubert Humphrey supporters; price-checking in store [?]; politics, 1977
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Includes: meetings; classes; parade float; Local 108 at Gimbels, Burke-Hartke support; Christmas; flood damage; workers outside of Eileen Hope
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Includes: retirees; fair; parade float; workers in shops, in front of Gimbels
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Includes: meetings; Milton Shapp; Local 108 outside of Gimbels; miscellaneous graphics
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Includes: meetings; bus trip; nursing aides; "Save Our Shops" protest; retirees; parties; COPE Awards, York
- Mixed photographs and negatives (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Includes: Belle Scott Deborah; Betty's party; workers on strike at Donna Lee; shop council, York, Lancaster, Harrisburg; shop council, 1968; Hilda's; Hubert Humphrey, 1968; Puerto Rico; "Tax News and Notes"
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Includes: workers in shops; speakers; meetings
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Includes: classes; AFL-CIO Union Industries Show, Washington, D.C.; picket outside of Woolworths; meetings; dresses; coffee break
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Includes: Unity House Northeast Institute, August 1960; John F. Kennedy supporters; meetings; leafletting in York; timecards; meetings; retirees; Pennsylvania AFL-CIO Education Institute; workers in shop; reading "Inside Public Welfare"
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Includes: meetings; sculptures; parties; Christmas
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Includes: meetings, strikers
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Includes: Christmas parties, Harrisburg and Lancaster, 1970; ice storm; picnic; meetings; Hesteco, Cameron Uniforms; Hanover 1968, York, Christmas party
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Includes: Terry, Cameron, M. Miles, Red Cross; retireers; shop council; antique cars; retirees, Christmas 1968, Lancaster, Lebanon; General Executive Board meeting, M. Miles committee, Hugh Mahoney; Harrisburg Christmas 1968
- Mixed photographs and negatives (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Includes: Shapp-Kline float; arthritis pictures; meetings
- Mixed photographs and negatives (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Includes: court house; Boderstein [?] Sesher [?] Garment negotiating committee; leafletting outside of Sears; on strike at Stevensville Dress Company, Hel-E Knit, Dinah Lynne, Donna Lee, Burkey Mills; protest at Lancaster Garment Company; Ethel Maid, Alpha Mills, Argo Knitting Mills; party
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 17)
  Includes: meetings; on strike at Nettie Frocks, Muriel Dress, Jefferson Outlet, Dinah Lynn, Eileen Hope, Donna Lee, [illegible] Corset, Perry Manufacturing; "Good Luck to the Girls, ILGWU"; reading "35 Northeast"
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 18)
  Includes: meetings; workers in shops; Mobile Health Center; retirees; strike; health survey team; Donegal negotiations, 1969
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Includes: retirees, Columbia; staff conference, Disney World; District Council Harrisburg negotiations; retirees bazaar, 1972; Pennsylvania Labor Committee for McGovern and Shriver; shop council, human relations, Dean Gross, Tidy [?] negotiations, 1970; Newport, ballet class; York Christmas party, 1970
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 20)
  Includes: New York City; on strike at [Paneco?]; meetings; recreation; York retirees club; office work; CLC; Penn State United Fund, scholarships, new shops, Red Lion, 1969; Unity House, Northeast Workers Education, Education Institute, 1969; Columbia retirees, Allenberry shop council, Allenberry district council, 1969
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Includes: Christmas party; event with Esther Peterson; E & O committee, Harrisburg; E & O committee, Lancaster; District Council [illegible]; Gerber, Gingold, [illegible]; Lebanon Christmas party, 1970; M. Mile, Northeast, Drug Department; Donegal negotiations, press conference, Terry negotiations, Red Cross award, Middletown, 1969; Rubenstein, Dallastown, District Council retirees, Penn Garment; Columbia retirees, community services, graduation, education classes, York, Croel [?] manufacturing
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 22)
  Includes: Burke-Hartke rally outside of JCPenny; meetings; convention, 1962; Union Label Week, 1960; York County Labor Council, Pennsylvania AFL-CIO COPE Institute, 1977
- Mixed photographs (Box 7, Folder 23)
  Includes: meetings; Christmas party; portraits; Bonnie Segal
- Mixed photographs and negatives (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Includes: Unity House, 1972; flood, Steelton, 1972; meetings; Las Vegas flight home; Bavarian Festival; Christmas party; District Council, Shop Council; District Council swearing-in; CLC class, Labor Academy, March 1968; Penn State Consumer, 1968; Union Label, Harrisburg, Lancaster; meetings; convention
- Mixed photographs (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Includes: Columbia retirees, finance committee, class; meetings; political strategists, Cameron retirees, retirees club and Columbia, DiAnne retirees, Lancaster retirees, strike at Nettie Frocks and Deborah; Pittsburgh AFL-CIO; human relations; shop council, York, Lancaster, Toni Matthews; Harrisburg shop council, 1969, R. Reuter, Lancaster shop council, Sally
- Mixed negatives (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Includes: Union Label; CLC class, Phil, B/pay; chair caning; Columbia retirees; Gingold, retiree, 4th ann[iversary?]; Kay retirement; CLC graduation, Lancaster graduation, December 1968; Reverend Posey; ILG Chorus, Lancaster 1969; Hesteco Press severance, military withdrawal; York, Harriburg, and Lancaster retireers, 1968; Mary V. with retiree items, York S/H council, 1968; convention, 1968
- Mixed photographs (Box 8, Folder 4)
  for publication, pages 1-7?
- Mixed photographs (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Includes: rally agains imports; meetings; class; event for Milton Shapp; Samco negotiaions [?]; parties; flood; Sargent-Shriver
- Mixed photographs (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Includes: meetings; parties; conventions; rallies; Atlantic Labor Press Conference; health care
- Mixed photographs (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Includes: meetings; Pennsylvania Labor Committee for McGovern-Shriver; Lattimer Massacre memorial unveiling with Cesar Chavez; recreation; retirees; stop imports rally
- Mixed photographs (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Includes: parties; rallies; performance; meetings; Christmas; retirees; Cameron Dress Company
- Mixed photographs (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Includes: meetings; Shapp-Kline election night; on strike at Martin Arsham Sewing Company; performance; retirees; workers in shops; Unity House
- Mixed photographs (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Includes: meetings; workers in shops; rally against imports
- Mixed photographs (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Includes: meetings, Christmas party
- Mixed negatives (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Includes: Las Vegas; Las Vegas with gowns and at night; Kay retirement; flood; Boulder Dam; import protest rally, April 13, 1977; election and objection committee, Local 196 and 197, convention, 1977; Litity Sports Victory party, February 1977
- Mixed graphics (Box 8, Folder 13)
  For "Garment Worker"?
- Oversize photographs, 1947-1962 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Includes: delegates to ILGWU convention, 1947; ILGWU convention, 1962; group photo (Coatesville, Pennsylvania); ILGWU convention, 1950; Committee on Education, ILGWU convention, 1959; delegates to ILGWU convention, 1950; ILGWU convention, 1959; untitled group photos